Do you like her? Do you like Nao?
佰合)好きなの? 菜緒ちゃんのこと なお
Yeah, I do. It's true.
うえはら (上原)そうだよ そういうことだから
You're going to be late.
遅刻すんぞ
Sorry! Go on ahead.
ごめん先行ってて まだ準備できてなくて
See you.
じゃあな
Do you like her? Do you like Nao?
佰合)好きなの? 菜緒ちゃんのこと
Yeah, I do.
そうだよ
You mean... he... likes me?
好きって…こと?
It's true.
そういうことだから
Seriously?
(まりな)マジで!?
No way! I can hardly believe it!
ウソ~何か信じらんない
What? Really?
えつそう?
Huh? No, that's not what I mean.
まりな)え?違う違う
I mean I never expected Uehara to say such a thing.
上原君がそんなふうに言うのが 意外ってこと 息外つC
Oh... Yeah.
ああ…うん
I kind of thought it was true.
そっちのほうは何となく 気づいてたからさ
Huh?
(菜緒)ん?
I thought Uehara just might like you.
上原君って菜緒のこと 好きなのかなーって
Huh? Really? How did you know?
えっウソ!何で?
Isn't it wonderful?
よかったねえ
Now you can be a real boyfriend and girlfriend.
これで本物の 彼氏と彼女ってわけだ
Uh...
あつえ…実は
I haven't told him I like him.
まだ好きって言ってない
You haven't told him you like him?
"まだ好きって言ってない,,!?
Don't shout it!
ちょっと声が大きいよ!
Why not? Huh?
何で?え?
I mean, I was so elated... I missed my chance to say it.
だって舞い上がっちゃつて こつ 言いそびれちゃった
Then from Uehara's perspective, it's one-sided love?
じゃあ上原君サイドから見れば 片思いってこと?
Wow! What an envious position you're in!
うわ~菜緒 なんて贅沢な身分
But I'm sure my feelings are totally obvious.
でも私の気持ちは バレバレだと思うし
-No, I don't think he's noticed. -Really?
いやバレてないでしよ (菜緒)え?
I mean, Uehara can't read feelings at all!
だって上原君 こつ 超鈍いじゃん
Well, you can't either.
まつ菜緒もだけど
Well, whatever. It's almost Valentine's Day anyway.
まあいいや もうすぐバレンタインだしね
It's your chance to tell him you like him.
ちゃんと好きって言う チャンスだよ
Valentine's Day?
バレンタイン...
Yep.
うん
Maybe I'll give it a shot.
ちょっと頑張ってみようかな
Nao! I'm so happy for you!
菜緒~ !よかったね
Good morning.
(菜緒)おはよう
Stop!
(大地)ストップ
-I'm sorry. -Like I said, don't apologize.
(菜緒)ごめんね (大地)だから謝んなって
Nao?
菜緒?
-What's wrong? -You're spacing out.
どうした? (光石)ボ ーツとして
It's nothing at all.
何でもない
I've got to study for the test.
テスト 勉強しなきゃ
I'll do my best!
頑張ろ
OK, pass them forward quickly.
(教師)はい じゃあ速やかに 後ろから回収するように
If you still can't master this stuff,
ここでつまずいたところは
it'll affect you in your senior year.
3年になってからも 引きずるからな
You'll be having entrance exams next year as well.
来年は 受験も控えてるんだから
If you couldn't do a problem, don't just leave it blank.
できなかったところは そのままにしておくんじゃないぞ
OK, put them here after they've been collected.
はーい回収したのは ここに置いて
What's with you?
何だよ
Sorry. You can eat alone today.
ごめん 今日1人で食べて
I need to talk with Marina.
は ? (菜緒) まりなと話あるから
-OK, goodbye. -Hey!
じゃ失礼しま~す 上原)おい
Yes?
はい
Well, it doesn't really matter,
まあ別にいいけど
but we're going to see each other every day when we're at home,
どうせ帰ったら 毎日顔合わせるんだから
so it's pointless to avoid me.
避けても無駄だぞ こて
I'm not really trying to avoid you.
べ…別に避けてなんかないもん
Oh, really?
あっそ つて の
You're so stupid. Why are you avoiding him?
まりな)バカだねえ 何で避けんの?
-Well... -Well what?
だって… こつ (まりな)だって何? な) たつ
I just feel kind of self-conscious.
ちょっと照れるなあって 思いまして
Hey! Why are you laughing?
えつちょっと何で笑うの?
What about you?
まりなだって よ!こつ みつちゃんに告白された時
-Well, it was-- -It was what?
あれは (菜緒)あれは? )ノ
Uh... well...
あついや…
-I guess I felt self-conscious. -See!
照れくさいねやっぱり (菜緒)ほら!
OK, but forget about me.
(まりな)あーもう 私の話はいいの!
You've got to make plans to do something together on Valentine's Day.
それよりバレンタインの約束は ちゃんとするんだよ
OK.
うん
Sometimes, for a change of pace,
たまにはさ気分を変えて
you need to go out on a date, right?
外でデートするのも いいんじゃない?
You know, arrange to meet somewhere.
どっかで待ち合わせとかしてさ
-A date? -Yeah.
デート. (まりな) うん な) づ
Done!
よし フフッ
Uehara!
上原君!
Sorry. Were you waiting long?
ごめん待った?
No. I just got here.
ううん 今来たとこ
Shall we go?
行こうか
OK.
うん
Uehara... I like you.
上原君好きです
I like you too.
俺もだよ
-I'm so hungry. -Do you like me?
(光石)腹減った- (菜緒) "俺のこと好きか?"
-What's with you, Nao? -Yes, very much! Smooch!
(光石)菜緒どうしたの? (菜緒) ,'大好きチュッ"あー! ユツ
Nao! Nao! Nao!
(まりな)菜緒菜緒菜緒?
Oh, Mitsuishi. Ah! Can I stay at your place on the 13th?
あつみつちゃん あっ! 13日の夜 ああ
Sure thing. He'd find out if you baked at home.
いいよ 家で作ったら ネタバレになっちゃうもんね
-Let's make chocolate together. -OK!
一緒に作ろっかチョコ (菜緒) うん!
Then on the 14th we'll meet somewhere.
で14日は 外で待ち合わせする!
-Perfect! -What are you guys talking about?
まりな)よし! (光石)何何何の相談?
-It's a secret. -What kind of chocolate should I make?
まりな)内緒 (菜緒)何のチョコがいいかな
Uehara is the type that prefers volume over quality.
でも上原君はやっぱ 質より量って感じだよねえ
A cake is probably better.
ケーキとかのほうが いいんじゃない?
-Uehara loves cake! -Great! Then let's make a cake!
上原君ケーキ大好き! (まりな) じゃあケーキにしよう
-I get something too? -Which cake?
俺のもあるよね? (まりな)何にしよっかな
Uhm...
あの…
Uehara.
上原君
Uhm, Uehara.
あのさ上原君
Hey, Uehara!
ちょっと上 君! 原
What? I can hear you.
何だよ聞こえてるよ
If you can hear me, then answer!
聞こえてんだったら こつたら 返事ぐらいしてよね
Since you've been avoiding me
避けられてるから
I thought you weren't talking to me.
俺呼んでるんじゃないかと思って
Jeez, you're mean.
意地悪だな
So, what is it?
何?
Are you studying for the tests?
テスト勉強してんの?
No, not especially.
いや特に
How can he get such good grades when he doesn't even study?
勉強してなくて 何であんなに成績いいの?
Was that all you wanted?
何?用それだけ?
Uh, no.
あついや…
-So, Uehara. -Yeah?
あのさ上原君 (上原)ん?
Uhm...
あの…
On Sunday the 14th--
14日の日曜ってさ
I've got work.
バイト
Oh, obviously.
だよねえ
It from the evening.
夕方からだけど
Do you have plans in the day?
じゃあお昼は?
Not especially.
別に
Then how about a date...
じゃあさデート.
day out together. How about a day out together?
でで…出かけない? 出かけない?
Where?
どこに?
We can decide that now.
それはこれから決めてから
Why?
何で?
You don't know why?
何でって...
It's the 14th.
14日だし
The 14th?
(上原) 142 仩原) 142
Yeah... the 14th.
うん14日
Oh! Hey, didn't you know?
ああ~ お前知ってるか? ~知
The Japanese are the only people who get all excited over Valentine's Day.
バレンタインに 踊らされてるのなんて
Every year they get all crazy like idiots.
毎年あんなバカみたいに 盛り上がって
Really?
そうなの?
It's pretty stupid.
くだらねえよな
You may call it stupid,
くだらないとか言っちゃつて
but I bet you get tons of chocolates at school every year.
毎年学校でいっぱい チョコもらってんでしょ?
How many do you get? Ten? 50?
何個もらってんの? 10個とか? 50個とか?
Don't tell me it's 100!
まさか100個とか?
Zero!
ゼロだよ
If I carelessly accepted any, they'd expect something in return.
下手に受け取って
Oh, I wouldn't want anything in return at all.
あっ私は全然全然 大丈夫だよ!
Milk pudding would be enough.
牛乳プリンだけあれば
See, you do want something.
期待してんじゃねえかよ
Well... yeah, kind of.
いや…そりゃちょっとね
-So, where were we? -Huh?
で何だっけ? (菜緒)え?
Aren't we going somewhere?
いやどっか行くんだろ?
You mean it's OK?
えついいの?
Yeah.
いいよ
-So that's a promise? -Yeah.
じゃあ約束ね! 仩原)おう や上
Really... Zero, huh?
そっか0個か
The top three must spend a very lonely Valentine's Day.
御三家も案外寂しい バレンタイン過ごしてんだね
Oh, yeah. Come to think of it, I did accept one.
あつそういえば 1個だけもらったわ
-Really? -From Yuri.
え? (上原)百合から
I should have known... he'd accept one from Yuri.
やっぱゆりりんからは もらうんだ
Focus! Focus!
集中集中
-Oh, Daichi! -Huh?
あっ大ちゃん (大地)ん?
Oh, good morning.
あつおはよう
Good morning.
おはよう
Do you have morning practice today?
今日も朝練ですか?
No. Just my own private work-out. I'll probably do it until graduation.
いやーまあ自主練だから 卒業まではやるかな
That's hard. Don't you think so, Nao?
大変 ねえ菜緒
Yeah.
うん
But as a senior, I can finally excuse myself from Sundays.
でも3年は日曜で いよいよ引退
Oh, I see.
そうなんだ
All the seniors have been accepted at schools,
3年全員進路が決まって 日曜に追い出し試合やるんだ
Oh, wow! That sounds like fun!
何それ楽しそう!
This is going to be our last game here, so everyone's inviting their friends.
ここで試合すんのも最後だから みんな友達とか誘って
They want to make it like a festival.
祭りみたいにやろうって 言ってんだけど
If you guys are free, why don't you come?
お前らも暇だったら 見に来いよ
Sunday...
BBRE...
-Sunday's kind of... -Huh?
日曜日はちょっと… (大地)ん?
You know, it's Valentine's Day.
あつほら バレンタインですしね
Oh, that's right.
ああそっか
Us guys decided in our excitement. We forgot it's Valentine's.
男だけで盛り上がって決めたけど バレンタインか
Sorry.
ごめんなさい
Don't worry about it at all.
(大地)いいよ全然 気にしないで
But we'll have a big party for your graduation. Right, Nao?
(まりな)あーでも
-Uh-huh. -I'm looking forward to it.
うん っ (大地)楽しみにしとく
See you.
じゃあな
Come on, you! What's with that look?
ちょっとなんつー顔してんの
-I can't help it. -Yes you can!
だって こつ (まりな)だってじゃないよ
Why can't you just act normal?
菜緒が普通 にしなくて どうすんの
I know I should, but...
分かってるけど
You don't have to worry about him
菜緒が心配しなくても
because he gets lots of attention from everyone else.
大ちゃんのことは 周りがほっとかないから!
Makes me a little jealous.
ちょっと悔しい
Hey, hold on.
休地あのさ
Nah, never mind.
やっぱやめた
I told her.
俺も言いましたよ
I told Nao clearly.
よしかわ 吉川にちゃんと言いましたから
OK, pass them up from the back.
(教師)はい後ろから集めて
It's over!
終わった
Yes! They're all over!
やった終わったー!
Nao! Let's make chocolates!
菜緒チョコ作るよ!
-Chocolates!
(菜緒)チョコ! (まりな)チョコ!
It's done!
(オープンの終了音) まりな)はい
-Take it out! Take it out! -It looks yummy!
まりな)はい取って取って (菜緒)おいしそう てつ
-Be careful! -Uh-huh.
(まりな)気をつけてよ (菜緒) うん
There we go.
よいしょ
Ta-da!
ジャーン!
Hmm, next one.
うーん次
Next.
次
Maybe... No, next one.
ああ…次
Next, next.
次 次
Nope.
ううん
Darn it all!
(菜緒)もう!
Ta-da!
ジャーン!
-Uh, Nao. -Yes?
まりな)菜緒さ (菜緒)ん?
-Has your taste changed? -Huh?
何か趣味変わった? (菜緒)え?
It's like, more mature, or something.
大人っぽくなったっていうか よつたつ 何というか
Well, that's because...
tha...
Don't tell me that... you're letting Yuri influence you.
まさかとは思うけど ゆりりん意識してる?
I mean, Uehara already told you he liked you!
あの上原君に 告白までされてるくせに
I know!
分かってるよ
-But-- -But what?
でも…な)でも? (まりな)でも?
Does it bother you?
気になる?
Last year at school he didn't accept any chocolates at all.
去年は学校でチョコ1つも もらわなかったのに
But he did accept one from Yuri.
ゆりりんからはもらったって
Of course he'd accept it. They're chocolates from someone he likes.
(まりな)そりゃもらうでしようよ 好きな人からのチョコだよ
Oh, I mean,
あついやあの
He liked! Past tense, right?
"好きだった"ね? さにつに 過去形
Yeah.
うん
I don't think you need to act like an adult and dress all mature
そんな無理して 大人っぽい格好して
when it doesn't suit you.
背伸びしなくたって こつ いいと思うよ
Uehara likes you the way you are now, Nao.
上原君は 今の菜緒を好きになった
Isn't that right?
でしよ?
Uh-huh.
うん
Even if you do act like an adult, you'll never be Yuri.
背伸びしたってゆりりんには こつ なれないんだから
Wait! Hold on!
あーあつちよつ...
Why don't you try this on?
これとかも着てみたら いいんじゃない?
-Huh? -Yep.
(菜緒)え? (まりな) うん な) っ
This might be nice.
いいかも
-Uh, Nao. -Huh?
菜緒さ (菜緒)ん?
Have you put on a little weight?
ちょっと太った? つに
Wait! Nao! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
あっちよっ...菜緒 ごめんごめん
Aren't you going to eat?
食わないの?
No, go ahead. Have it.
うん 食べて食べて
You're weird.
変な奴
Oh, yeah. Uehara, about Sunday,
あっ上原君 日曜なんだけどさ
let's meet at 9:00 a.m. at the Red Brick Warehouse.
9時に赤レンガ倉庫前 待ち合わせで
Then at 10:00 a.m. we'll ride the Ferris wheel at Cosmo World...
10時にコスモワールドで 観覧車乗って
-Hold on a second here. -Huh?
ちよちよちよ (菜緒)ん?
What's that all about?
何それ
Our date schedule for Sunday.
日曜のデートプラン フン
-What?
仩原)え? (菜緒)え?
You don't like Ferris wheels?
観覧車イヤ?
-No, the part before that is weird. -Huh?
いやその前が変だろ (菜緒)え?
Why do we have to meet somewhere when we live together?
いやいや 何で一緒に住んでんのに
But meeting somewhere is part of a date.
デートと言ったら 待ち合わせでしょ?
Oh, don't worry. I'll be staying over at Marina's tomorrow.
あっ大丈夫 私明日はまりなんち泊まるから
Just so we can meet?
待ち合わせのために?
Uh, well, I've got other things to prepare too.
うんまあ いろいろ準備はあるけどね
Which do you like better, chocolates or cakes?
チョコとチョコレートケーキ どっちが好き?
-That question makes things obvious. -Who cares. Which one?
露骨な質問 (菜緒)いいからどっち?
The one that fills me up.
腹の足しになるほう
Got it. Cake, huh?
はいはい ケーキね
Speaking of which...
ちなみに…
what did you get from Yuri last year?
去年はゆりりんから 何もらったの?
What does that mean?
何それ
She's also the kind that prefers volume over quality.
あいつも 質より量って感じだからさ
Yeah, you're right.
だよね
-Yo! -Oh, Daichi.
よ つ (光石)お一大地先輩
-The tests are over, right? -Yeah, finally.
テスト終わったんだろ? (光石)やっとですよ
That's good.
お疲れ
So, did she do all right?
あいつ大丈夫だったのかな
-You mean Nao? -Yeah.
菜緒ですか? 休地うん
You haven't talked to her?
話してないんですか?
Well, stuff's happened.
まあいろいろあって
When I say stuff, I mean...
いろいろっていうか.
she turned me down.
フラれた
Really?
(光石)え...
Lately Nao never smiles when she's with me.
最近菜緒俺の前で 笑わなくなっちゃつてさ
Well, yeah... I can see that.
そりゃまあ…ですよね
-I'm sorry. -Like I said, don't apologize.
ごめんね (大地)だから謝んなって なつ
I never wanted to make her look like that.
あんな顔させたかったわけじゃ ないんだけどな
Huh?
(光石)はい?
Oh, it's nothing.
いや何でもない
You mean you're giving up on her?
諦めるってことですか?
Your meal's ready.
(徹平)賄いできたよ
Go ahead and eat, Nao.
いっせい (一星)吉川食っていいぞ
Today I don't need it.
今日は賄いいらない
What? Is something wrong with your stomach?
(一星)何だ 腹の調子でも悪いのか?
No, it's not that.
ううんそういうんじゃなくて
I'm just not hungry.
お腹すいてないだけ
Don't tell me you're dieting.
もしかしてダイエットとか?
You're dieting again?
(阿部)吉川何でまた?
I've gotten a little chubby lately.
最近太り気味で
Did your boyfriend tell you that?
(一星) あの彼氏に言われたとか?
He's not my boyfriend!
彼氏じゃないし!
Lately I've been making a lot of chocolate cakes.
最近チョコレートケーキの 試作品とかいっぱい作って
I ate too much of them.
食べすぎちゃつて
Is it for Valentine's Day?
もしかしてバレンタインの? (菜緒) うん
-I'll take it even if you don't mean it. -Sorry, Abe.
義理で全然いいからさ (菜緒)ごめんあべっち
This year I'm only giving one to the person I'm serious about.
今年は本命1本って 決めてるんだ
I thought finally this year I'd end up with at least one.
今年こそはゼロじゃないって 思ったのに
You mean you're not giving me one either?
お前今間接的に 俺にもくれないって言ったな
-No, I'm not. Sorry. -Wow, that was awfully direct.
ごめんなさい (一星) うわっストレートだな こな
In any case,
まあとにかく
I don't care whether it's Valentine's Day or bikini season,
うちはバレンタインだろうが 水着の季節だろうが
you have to eat. It's store policy.
賄い抜くの禁止だから 店の方針 ご
I like a woman that's a little chubby and enjoys eating.
ちょっとぐらい丸くたって こつ
Besides, how can you expect to work on an empty stomach?
大体な腹減って いい仕事できるかっつーの
What if you broke another bowl?
また丼割ったら どうしてくれんだよ
So you're worried about the bowls.
丼の心配ね
Just eat already!
(一星)いいから食えよ
Fine.
はーい
Take care.
(一星)お疲れさん
See you later.
お先にいっちゃん
You've forgotten to change.
お前着替え忘れてるぞ?
No, I didn't.
違うよ
The ramen was so good that I ate too much,
賄いがおいしすぎて 食べすぎちゃつたから
so I thought I'd jog all the way home.
うちまでジョギングして 帰ろうかなーと思って
Uehara didn't say a word. I'm serious.
本当に上原君に 言われたわけじゃないからね
I just thought I'd like to lose some weight, that's all.
ただ自分で勝手に 痩せたいなあって思っただけ
Hey, hold on a second.
めあちょっと待ってて
-Huh? -Just wait here.
(菜緒)ん? (一星)いいから待ってろ
-OK, let's jog! -What?
よし走るぞ るて (菜緒)え?
I'm going to the convenience store, so I'll jog with you until there.
コンビニまで行くから 途中まで付き合うよ
-What? -Hurry up!
(菜緒)え? (一星)早くしろ
Hey! Hey, wait up!
(菜緒) ちょっ…ちょっと待ってよ
Yes?
(菜緒)はーい
-Good evening! -Oh, Yuri!
(百合) こんばんは (菜緒)あーゆりりん!
-What's up? -Uh, I just...
どうしたの? 佰合) うんちょっとね
Oh, I brought a really delicious cake.
あつおいしいケーキ 買ってきたんだ
-Can I come in? -Yes, of course.
上がっていい? (菜緒) うんもちろん
-Thank you. -Go ahead.
(百合)お邪魔しまーす (菜緒)はーい
Hey there!
(ドアが開く音) おっす!
Why are you here?
どうしたんだよ
Why are you looking so worried? Nothing's wrong.
そんな怖い顔しないでよ 何もないわよ
I just came over to give this to Nao.
今日はこれを 菜緒ちゃんに届けに来ただけ
-Huh? What is it? -Open it and have a look.
(菜緒)えっ何? (百合)開けてみて ロノ 1开
Really?
えつ
It's a present for you, Nao.
菜緒ちゃんにプレゼント
What? Really?
えついいの?
Uh-huh. I wanted to say thank you.
うん お礼したかったんだ
I caused you so much trouble.
菜緒ちゃんにはすっかり 迷惑かけちゃつたからさ
I'm sorry.
ごめんね
Yuri... Thank you.
ゆりりん…ありがとう
What?
佰刽何? 合
-You caused me tons of trouble too. -Oh, yeah. This dress,
俺も相当迷惑してるんだけど 佰合)あつこれ
-it also came in blue. -It's OK. I like this color.
もう1色青があったんだけど つにんに (菜緒) この色好き
I thought so. I was sure you'd like this one more.
だよね菜緒ちゃんは 絶対こっちだと思った
I'm so happy.
(菜緒) うれしい
Oh, sorry. What were you saying?
あつごめん 何だっけ?
How's my brother? Busy, as usual?
(上原)兄貴は? 相変わらず忙しいのか?
Yeah, so it seems.
(百合)みたいね
You're looking awfully pale.
お前顔色最悪だな
Are you all right, Yuri?
(菜緒)大丈夫?ゆりりん
I had too much to drink at an office get-together yesterday.
昨日会社の飲み会で 飲みすぎちゃつて
-I'm all right. -Haven't you heard?
ああ大丈夫だよ (上原)知ってるか?
Even if it's over drinks,
酒の席での暴言も 勤務査定に響くらしいぞ
You're kidding!
ウソ
I've been meaning to tell you this for a while.
ずっと言おうと 思ってたんだけどさ
What?
佰刽何よ
You're the type that causes trouble when you drink.
百合って 酒で身を滅ぼすタイプだよな
You're just fine, Yuri. Just fine.
大丈夫だよゆりりん 全然大丈夫
Oh, Nao.
(百合)菜緒ちゃーん
Oh, I think I'll try this on.
(菜緒)あっ私 これ着てこよつかな
-Yeah, I want to see it. -OK.
(百合) うん見たい! (菜緒) うん んん
Something's happened, hasn't it?
(上原)何かあったんだろ?
I told you, nothing's wrong.
佰刽 何もないって言ってるでしょ
Then don't come over suddenly like this.
だったら突然来んなよ
Oh, were you worried about me?
あっ心惋しちゃった? つに
Of course I'd worry.
心配ぐらいするだろ
You're my sister-in-law after all, for some strange reason.
(上原)曲がりなりにも 義理の姉なんだから
"For some strange reason"?
(百合)曲がりって
Jeez, you're always so emotionally unsteady.
ったくいつまでも フラフラしやがって
How dare you say that!
うるさいわね!
How dare I say it? Then don't come over if it's not true.
仩原) "うるさいわね"じゃねーよ じゃ来んなよ
Why not? I can if I like.
(百合)何で別にいいじゃん
-Here. It's a cake. -I don't want it.
ほらケーキ (上原)いらねーよんなもん
OK, fine!
佰刽あっそ
Oh, here it is. That something cake from somewhere.
おーこれこれ どっかの何とかってケーキ
Yuri seemed like she'd lost weight.
ゆりりん少し痩せてたね
Really?
(上原)そうか?
You know you noticed.
気づいてるくせに
Huh? Did you say something?
ん?何か言った?
No, nothing.
ううん何でもない
Uh-oh.
あつ
Aw, jeez.
ったく つに
I'll be back in a minute.
ちょっと行ってくる
Yuri!
百合!
You forgot these.
忘れもん
Sorry.
ごめん
Nao.
菜緒
Huh?
(菜緒)ん?
Oh, dear!
(まりな)あ~あ
-It's OK. It's OK. -I'm sorry.
大丈夫大丈夫 (菜緒)ごめん
Oh, actually,
あーねえそれよりさ
could you taste this?
これ味見して (菜緒)え?
I'll try it.
よいしょ
Yeah, you're right!
うん本当だ
Huh? What?
ちょっと...え?
You've got some on you.
ついてるよ
-Where? Get it off. -Your chin.
(まりな)どこどこ?取って (菜緒)アゴアゴアゴ
That's really cute.
かわいい
Yuri gave it to me.
(菜緒) ゆりりんからもらったの
Nao?
菜緒?
She sure is.
本当
She's absolutely perfect.
完璧すぎて
It feels like I'm becoming more and more selfish.
何か私 だんだん欲張ってる気がする
What do you mean?
ん?
Before, I thought that I didn't mind that he liked Yuri.
前はねゆりりんのこと
But since Uehara said he likes me,
上原君に 好きって言われてからさ
the stuff I thought couldn't be helped...
今までしょうがないって 思ってたことが...
You won't tolerate anymore?
許せなくなってきた?
No, it's not that I won't tolerate it, but...
いや許せないとかじゃ ないけど
I'm not sure how to put it.
何て言ったらいいか 分かんないな
You mean, "Don't be nice to any woman besides me."
"私以外に優しくしないで!”って
No, it's not that bad.
いやそこまで 言えるほどでもないし
That's exactly the kind of thing you should say.
いやむしろ言ってこうよ! 誰だってイヤでしょ
when the guy you like is kind to another woman.
好きな人が自分以外に 優しくすんのなんて
Is that what this is?
そういうもん?
Yes, that's what this is.
そういうもんです!
But, Uehara did say that he likes you, right?
でも上原君は 菜緒が好きって言ったんでしょ?
Uh-huh.
うん
He told it to Yuri too, right?
ゆりりんに言ったんでしょ?
Well, then in that case--
だったらさ
I know, but...
分かってるけど
But I've been around him so much.
でもずっと見てきたから
I know that Yuri's special to him.
上原君がゆりりんのこと 大事に想ってるの 相
That's it! No more talk of this!
(まりな)はい この話はここで終わり
Yeah, you're right.
そうだね
Besides, I'm going to spend all day with Uehara tomorrow.
明日は上原君と1日 ずつと一緒にいられるし
That's right.
そうだよ
You've got to tell him your feelings tomorrow too.
明日はちゃんと 気持ちを伝えないとね
Now I'm getting all nervous.
何か緊張してきた
Jeez, Nao! Pull yourself together.
ったく菜緒 しっかりしてよ!
-I'm worried. -Stop it!
どうしよう (まりな)大丈夫
The cake is perfect.
ケーキはバッチリできたし
All you have to do is say, "I like you" and give it to him.
あとはちゃんと 好きって言って渡すだけ
I'm sure Uehara will be pleased.
上原君も きっと喜んでくれると思うよ
OK.
うん
You can do it, Nao!
頑張れ菜緒 米
I will.
うん
-Thanks for coming.
(上原)ありがとうございました (明)ありがとうございました
You can go now, Uehara.
(明)上原君そろそろいいよ
OK.
はい (明) うん
-Uehara! -Yeah?
ひさし (ななこ)久志君! 仩原)おう
Here, this is for you.
はいこれ
Oh, I don't accept any chocolate.
(上原)あっ俺チョコはいい
I know that.
それは分かってる
Then why'd you make it?
じゃあ何で 何で作ったんだよ つにんに
-You made me taste tons of them. -Because I made up my mind.
俺に試作品何個も食わさせて (ななこ)決めたの
Once I gave this to Uehara, I'd forget about him,
これ渡したらきっぱり 久志君のこと忘れて
and get serious about entrance exams.
受験に専念する
Then I'll get into the same high school as Uehara.
それで久志君と同じ高校に 受かってみせる
That's still not forgetting about him.
それじゃ忘れたってことには ならないよね
You'll still be thinking about him the whole time.
それずっと覚えてるって ことだもんね
Thanks.
ありがとう
Do your best on those exams.
受験頑張れよ
What's wrong with you? Why are you crying, Dad?
(ななこ)意味分かんない 何でお父さんが泣いてるの?
It makes me so sad to see my own daughter heartbroken.
(明)だって娘の失恋は こつ お父さん悲しいよ
I'm not heartbroken. I'm just giving up for a while.
失恋じゃないし 一時休戦で
Oh, come on, Dad!
ちょっとお父さん
-He rejected you. -No he didn't!
フラれちゃつたな (ななこ)フラれてないってば よいつ
-Your first rejection. -He didn't reject me!
(明)初めてか初失恋か (ななこ)フラれてないってば よいつ
-Come on, let's have a drink. -Yeah, just one more.
(男1)飲み行こうよいいじゃん (男2)そうだよもう一軒!
Well, let me think. I'm quite a handful when I'm drunk, you know.
(百合)どうしよつかなあ 私酔っ払うと大変だよ?
-You won't be able to handle me. -Really?
手に負えないかも (男1)どう大変なの?
Yuri?
百合?
I kiss everyone I see.
超キス魔だからさ
-Cool! That's perfect! -Come on, let's go!
(男2)いいじゃんそれ最高! 行こう行こう.
-It feels like this was meant to be. -Over here!
何か運命感 ちゃうよね (男1)あっちあっち じ
I'm sorry for the trouble she's caused.
ご迷惑をおかけしました
-Uehara? -Let's go.
久志? 仩原)行くぞ
Hey! Hold it right there! Who the hell are you?
おいちょっと待てよ お前誰だよ
Oh! Sorry! Sorry! This is my little brother.
あーごめんごめん これ弟
-Little brother? -He's always meddling in my business.
(男2)弟? (百合)そうおせっかいな奴でさ
Bye, Uehara. OK, let's go for another drink.
じゃあね久志 私はもう一軒行くから
Quit trying to push me around!
偉そうにしないでよ
Uh-oh!
おおつ
-Come on, let's get out of here. -Yeah.
行こうぜもう (男2)ああ
I'll take you home.
送る
No, I'm not going back home.
いやうちには帰んない
What's happened this time?
今度は何があったんだよ つにんに
Takuya's away on business.
卓也出張でいないんだ
Let me stay there tonight.
今日泊めてよ
Jeez! Quit it with that look!
うわっ 何そのイヤそうな顔
OK, fine! Then I'm going to go drinking.
あつそ じゃあやっぱり飲み行く
Hey you guys! Hold on there!
お兄さーんちょっと待って
Let's go.
仩原)行くぞ
-Get in. -I'm here, Nao!
仩原)ほら (百合)ただいま菜緒ちゃん
-She's not here. -What?
(上原)いないよ 佰合)え?
She's staying over at a friend's house.
仩原) 友達んとこ泊まりに行ってる
-Then I'm going home. -Hey!
(百合)私やっぱ帰る 仩原)おい
-It's too late to be going anywhere. -Let go of me!
こんな時間にどこ行くんだよ 佰刽離して
You OK?
大丈夫か?
God damn you.
(百合)バカ野郎
-What was that for? -You liar.
何だよ突然 佰合)ウソつき
I hate you.
パーカ
I wonder if he's asleep.
寝てんのか な
Oh, shit!
ヤツベ
-Hello? -I'm sorry, Nao.
(菜緒)もしもし (上原)悪い吉川
Wait for me. I'll be there in a bit.
待ってて すぐ行くから
You overslept?
寝坊した?
Yeah, sorry.
ごめん
It's OK. I'll be waiting.
うんじゃあ待ってるね
Yuri.
百合?
Takuya's going to be transferred overseas it seems.
卓也海外転勤みたい
Really?
え?
I saw some documents he'd hidden in the car.
車に隠してあった資料 見ちゃつたんだよね つにんに
What's this?
え?
He'll be going to Australia.
オーストラリアだって
It looks like he plans to go alone.
卓也1人で行くつもりみたい
But why?
何でだよ?
You brothers are both alike.
あんたたち兄弟似てるじゃん
You can do everything alone.
1人で何でもできて
He's probably fine without me.
私なんかいなくても 大丈夫だからでしょ?
He was probably consulting with his ex-girlfriend this whole time.
元カノにはずっと 相談してたみたいだし
They might even... be going together.
もしかして一緒に行くのかも
What are you talking about?
何だよそれ
Things he can't say to me...
私には言えないことも
he talks about to his ex-girlfriend.
元カノには話せるんだよ るんに
But I was left in the dark.
私だけ何も知らなくて
This is just so stupid.
バカみたい
Why did he even marry me if he was going to be this way?
だったら こつた 何で私と結婚したのよ
I wish I'd never married him.
結婚なんか しなきゃよかったじゃん
You've got a fever.
坴丸? 熱
Forget about me.
ほっといてよ
Hello? Where are you now?
もしもし 今どこ?
-I'm sorry, Nao. -What?
(上原)吉川 ?ごめん (菜緒)え?
I can't go.
(上原)行けなくなった aつ
-Huh? -Go ahead and go home.
(上原)先帰ってて え
Did something happen?
何かあったの?
Does it have to do with Yuri?
もしかしてゆりりん?
I'm sorry, Nao.
(上原)ごめん吉川
I'll be home soon. Just wait a--
すぐ帰るから 少し待つ
No!
(菜緒)イヤ
Huh?
え?
I knew it. You still prefer Yuri, don't you?
(菜緒)結局 上原君はゆりりんなんだね
Nao?
吉川?
Come on. Let's go.
おい 行くぞ
You said it though... that you'd gotten over her.
言ったじゃん 吹っ切れたって
that you like me.
私のこと好きって
We'll do this next week instead, OK?
(駿介)来週 仕切り直しましょうね先輩!
Yeah, if it's sunny.
(大地) うん晴れたらな
-See you later! -Bye.
(部員たち)お疲れさまです (大地)お疲れ
Take care.
気をつけろよ
Nao.
(大地)菜緒
What happened to you? You're soaking wet!
お前どうしたんだよ ずぶ濡れじゃん
What about you, Daichi? Don't you have a game?
大ちゃんこそ試合は?
No, it's raining.
いや雨だから
Oh, yeah. I guess you're right.
そっか だよね
Nao?
菜緒?
Daichi, you're a rain man, aren't you?
大ちゃん雨男だっけ? こつ
No, it's you, Nao. You're the rain woman.
いや菜緒だろ雨女は
Oh, yeah. That's right.
そうだった
Weren't you supposed to meet that guy somewhere?
お前あいつと会う約束 してたんじゃないのか?
Yeah... we were.
うん してた
Oh, that must be why.
ああだからか
That must be why it's raining.
だから雨降っちゃつたんだね つにんに
Sorry, Daichi.
ごめんな大ちゃん
I'm sorry.
ごめん
I'm sorry, I...
ごめん私…